AHJEONG SEO

Samsung Research

https://ahjeongseo.github.io

+82 10 7402 9803 \$\phi\$ rubyrang2@snu.ac.kr \$\phi\$ ahjeong.seo@samsung.com

RESEARCH INTEREST

My primary research goal is to **develop robustly reasoning AI like humans** through structured and disentangled inference. I'm especially interested in the explicit and robust reasoning process via traversing over concept graphs constructed with neuro-symbolic approaches. Currently, I am researching improving logical reasoning performances of large-scale models with this method in Samsung Research.

RESEARCH PUBLICATIONS

Neuro-Symbolic Graph Reasoning for Robust Inference in Neural Sequence Models (in preparation)

<u>Ahjeong Seo</u>, Joohyung Lee, *The First Workshop on UM-IoS: Unimodal and Multimodal Induction of Linguistic Structures (EMNLP 2022 Workshop)*December 2022

Attend What You Need: Motion-Appearance Synergistic Networks for Video Question Answering Ahjeong Seo, Gi-Cheon Kang, Junhan Park, Byoung-Tak Zhang, The Joint Conference of the 59th Annual Meeting of the Association for Computational Linguistics and the 11th International Joint Conference on Natural Language Processing (ACL-IJCNLP 2021)

August 2021

DramaQA: Character-Centered Video Story Understanding with Hierarchical QA

Seongho Choi, Kyoung-Woon On, Yu-Jung Heo, <u>Ahjeong Seo</u>, Youwon Jang, Minsu Lee, Byoung-Tak Zhang, Proceedings of the Thirty-Fifth AAAI Conference on Artificial Intelligence (AAAI 2021) February 2021

Sparse Self-Attention Mechanism for Learning Sequential Video Data

Ahjeong Seo, Kyoung-Woon On, Byoung-Tak Zhang, Korea Software Congress 2019 (KSC 2019) December 2019

WORK EXPERIENCE

AI Methods Team, Samsung Research

Aug. 2021 - Now

Researcher (Adviser: Joohyung Lee)

Seoul. Korea

- · Large-Scale AI: Researching a dual-system model complementing the reasoning limitations of Samsung's large-scale model applications with a neuro-symbolic graph approach, and planning to submit a paper to the EMNLP 2022 Workshop.
- · Neuro-Symbolic Contents Search: Developed a search engine for movie contents considering both lexical and semantic clues in queries. Specifically, experimented with neural models for semantic search, contributed to a keyword search engine with Elastic Search, and collected and cleaned content data.

RESEARCH PROJECT

Video Turing Test

Sep. 2019 - Aug. 2021

Researcher at Seoul National University (Adviser: Byoung-Tak Zhang)

- Research (AAAI 2022, ACL 2021): Aimed to build an AI with human-level intelligence for video understanding, conducted research to allow the AI to robustly and explicitly reason via structuring information based on interdisciplinary knowledge. Proposed a model combining divided visual signals depending on texts for multimodal reasoning based on human visual processing for ACL 2021. Recommended the DramaQA dataset and a baseline model for hierarchical video understanding based on human cognitive development stages for AAAI 2021.
- · Organizing Challenges and Workshops (ECCV 2020, ICCV 2019): Participated in organizing DramaQA challenges and Video Turing Test workshops, managed EvalAI challenge server, and built the homepage: https://dramaqa.snu.ac.kr/

EDUCATION

Seoul National University

Master of Science in Neuroscience

Interdisciplinary Program in Neuroscience (Adviser: Byoung-Tak Zhang)

Thesis: Motion-Appearance Synergistic Networks for Video Question Answering

Hanyang University Mar. 2014 - Aug. 2019

Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Engineering, Minoring in Industrial Engineering

Department of Computer Engineering

Seoul, Korea

Seoul, Korea

Sep. 2019 - Aug. 2021

INTERNSHIP

Clova Biz AI, Naver Corp. Apollo Backend, Naver Corp. Nov. 2018 - Feb. 2019 Jul. 2018 - Aug. 2018

InternSeongnam-si, Korea

· Experimented with ML models for a website project and various service demonstrations

· Generated and pre-processed data, built docker environment and APIs, and developed website with Spring Framework, jQuery Ajax, HTML, and CSS.

HONORS AND AWARDS

International Short-Term Dispatch Program Scholarship, Hanyang University Jun. 2016 Dean's Encouragement Award, Hanyang University Nov. 2014 Honors Scholarships, Hanyang University Sep. 2014

EXTRA-CURRICULAR

Algorithm Club at Hanyang University

Mar. 2014 - Aug. 2019

· Participated in algorithm study groups, and received Dean's Encouragement Award in an in-school competition Hanyang University Buddy Assistants Jan. - Feb. 2018

Organized and participated in many activities and helped foreign students adapt to Korean culture and life

Short-term Overseas Dispatch Program, University of Indonesia Exchange Student, Nanyang Technological University

Jul. - Aug. 2016 Jan. - May 2016

Developed cultural competence via activities ranging from field-trips to participating in a school club.

SKILLS AND LANGUAGE

Technical Skills Pytorch, Tensorflow, Python, C++, C, HTML, R, Java

Language Proficiency Fluent in English and Native in Korean

REFERENCES

Byoung-Tak Zhang

Professor

Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Brain Science, and Cognitive Science College of Engineering, Seoul National University E-mail: btzhang@bi.snu.ac.kr

Phone: +82 2-880-1833(office), 880-1847(secretary) https://bi.snu.ac.kr/~btzhang/

Joohyung Lee

Associate Professor / Vice President at Samsung Research

School of Computing, Informatics, and Decision Systems Engineering (CIDSE)

Fulton Schools of Engineering, Arizona State University

AI Methods Team, Samsung Research E-mail: j00hyung.lee@samsung.com

http://peace.eas.asu.edu/joolee/index.html Phone: $+82\ 2-6147-3280$

Sanghwa Lee

Research Professor

Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering E-mail: lsh529@snu.ac.kr College of Engineering, Seoul National University Phone: $+82\ 10-6238-9198$